Guide to the Arthur E. Jones Architectural Records, 1936-1989 MS 535
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Arthur E. Jones Architectural Records
1936-1989
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Jones, Arthur Evan
MS 535
8 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
The Arthur Jones Architectural Records contain information and pictures of projects Jones was involved with in his career with Houston-based Lloyd and Morgan, Lloyd, Jones, and Brewer, and Jones and Fillpot.
Biographical Note
Arthur E. Jones, a 1947 Rice University graduate, joined the Houston firm of Hermon F. Lloyd and William B. Morgan that year, and became partner in 1961. In 1974 the firm became Lloyd Jones and Associates, and by 1976 adding Benjamin E. Brewer, Jr. to become Lloyd, Jones and Brewer. By 1984 Brewer left the firm and Bob G. Fillpot joined. Hermon F. Lloyd died in 1989 and the last incarnation of the form was Jones and Fillpot. Jones' projects with the firms, which were primarily but not only in Houston, include the Astrodome, the Allen Centers, the Melrose building, and various buildings in Greenway Plaza, the University of Houston, and Rice University.
Scope and Contents
The Arthur E. Jones Architectural Records contain photographs, slides, renderings, and information about projects during his career with Lloyd and Morgan, Lloyd, Jones, and Brewer, and Jones and Fillpot. The firms' projects were primarily based in Houston. Series I includes information about the firms and administrative and project details. Series II contains images, further information, and awards for projects, and Series III are oversized material of several projects including drawings of the Astrodome. Photographers of items in the collection include Richard Payne, Bob Bailey, Balthazar Korab, and André Kertész.
Arrangement note
Missing Title
Series I: Administrative (1936-1989)
Series II: Projects (1948-1989)
Series III: Oversize (1948-1989)
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The materials were given to Woodson Research Center by Arthur E. Jones in 2008
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Index Terms
Subjects
Architecture -- Texas -- Houston -- 20th century; Architects -- Texas; Architecture
Document Types
blueprints (reprographic copies); architectural drawings (visual works); photographs
Places
Houston (Texas) -- Buildings, structures, etc.
Subjects (Persons)
Locke, Al; McGrath, Chas; Meyer, Art; Miller, John P.; Miller, Ralph N.; Morgan, William B.; Murdy, W. D.; Payne, Richard; Peters, George; Peters, Paul; Richburg, Jack; Rosenthal, Steve; Seiders, F. Wilbur; Smusz, Ben; Stewart, Ed; St. Gil, Marc; Thomas, Jim; Whitney, Peter; Bailey, Bob; Begham, Stan; Aker, Joe C., photographer; Alonso, Gabriel; Gardner, Rick; Fillpot, Robert G.; Fisk, David; Dorsey, Paul; Brewer, Benjamin E., Jr.; Johnson, Owen; Hester, Paul, 1948-; Henrikson, Vernon R.; Gilbert, Earl R.; Georges, Alexandre; Lloyd, Hermon F.; Lieberman, Nathaniel; Laws, Jack F.; Korab, Balthazar; Kiger, Jennifer M.; Kertesz, Andre; Jones, Arthur Evan
Subjects (Corporations)
Milstead Photography.; Photographic Laboratories.; Seawell Photography.; Shoemake-Stiles Photography.; Stiles and Associates.; Woodallen Industrial Photography.; Foto Art Studios.; Dorsey and Peters.; Bisett and Dixon Photographers.; Harper Leiper Studios.; Gulf Photo.; Lawless and Son, Photographers.
- Series I: Administrative, 239265
  - Firm history and philosophy, project-related, 239270 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Project detail sheets, 239269 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Projects - alphabetical listing, 239268 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Projects - numerical listing, 239267 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Projects by completion date listing, 239266 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series II: Projects, 239101
  - Aetna Insurance Company Building, 239264 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - [Herbert] Allen residence, completed 1976; 239263 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen Center, 239262 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents note
    photographs by Rick Gardner and Richard Payne
  - Allen Center 1 and 2, completed 1979; 239261 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allen Center 3, completed 1980; 239260 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allen Center 4 [Four Allen Center], completed 1984; 239259 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    photographs by David Fisk, Paul Hester, Chas McGrath, and Richard Payne
  - Allen Center 4 [Four Allen Center], completed 1984; 239258 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Allen Center - Capital Bank, completed 1980; 239257 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    photographs by Richard Payne
  - Allen Center - Capital Bank Heritage Club, completed 1981; 239256 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Allen Center - Meridien Hotel, completed 1980; 239255 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Allen Center - Meridien Hotel, completed 1980; 239254 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Allied Bank, completed 1983; 239253 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    photographs by Rick Gardner
  - Allied Bank - Century Club, completed 1984; 239252 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    photographs by chas McGrath
  - American Bank - Corpus Christi, TX, completed 1979; 239251 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - American Fore Insurance Group, 239250 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    photographs by Woodallen Industrial Photographers
  - American General, 239249 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    photographs by Balthazar Korab, Richard Payne, and Jim Thomas
  - American General Health Club, completed 1984; 239248 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    photographs by Chas McGrath
  - American General Life Buildings, completed 1965; 239247 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American General Riviana Building, completed 1974; 239246 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    photographs by Balthazar Korab and Richard Payne
  - American General Tower, 239245 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    photographs by Alexandre Georges, Harper Leiper Studios, Balthazar Korab, Milstead Photography, Richard Payne, Jim Thomas, and Woodallen Industrial Photographers
  - Americana Building, completed 1961; 239244 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    photographs by Harper Leiper Studios, Vernon R. Henrikson and Associates, and Stiles and Associates
  - American National Bank Building - Austin, TX, completed 1975; 239243 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    photographs by Harper Leiper Studios and Lawless and Son
  - Astrodome [Harris County Domed Stadium], completed 1965; 239242 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    photographs by Gulf Photo, Art Meyer Photography, and Paul Peters
  - Astrodome [Harris County Domed Stadium], completed 1965; 239241 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Astrodome - Planning and scheduling, 239240 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Astrodome - Planning and scheduling, 239239 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Astrodome - Planning correspondence, 239238 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Astrodome - Planning and specifications correspondence, 239237 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Astrodome - Planning and specifications correspondence, 239236 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Astrodome - Specifications, 239235 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Astrohall / Astroarena, completed 1966; 239234 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    photographs by Al Locke
  - Atlantic City [NJ] Convention Center, completed 1984; 239233 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    photographs by Nathaniel Lieberman
  - Banc Texas Allen Parkway, completed 1983; 239232 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - [Mrs. Ann] Bart residence - Stillforest, 239231 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - [Mrs. B.F.] Bart residence - Troon Road, completed 1948; 239230 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    photographs by Andre Kertesz (copyright Conde Nast Publications)
  - Bellaire [TX] Presbyterian Church, 239229 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bland-Willis Cadillac Company, completed 1970; 239228 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Block 298 garage and office building, completed 1982; 239227 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Block 321 garage and office building (Allen Center), completed 1980; 239226 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Boca Raton [FL] Financial Center, 239225 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Boston [MA] stadium, 239224 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    photographs by Paul Peters
  - Britton Building, completed 1962; 239223 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    photographs by Peter Whitney
  - Calcasieu Marine National Bank, Lake Charles, LA, completed 1983; 239222 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    photographs by Chas McGrath and Ed Stewart
  - Calcasieu Marine National Bank, Lake Charles, LA, completed 1983; 239221 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    photographs by Rick Gardner, Chas McGrath, and Ed Stewart
  - Calcasieu Marine National Bank - Executive interiors and club, 239220 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Calcasieu Marine National Bank - Executive interiors and club, 239219 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - [William] Cameron and Company, 239218 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Central Methodist Church, 239217 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Century/Mobil Oil Co. office building, 239216 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - [Mr. and Mrs. Virgil] Childress residence, 239215 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Christ the Servant Lutheran Church, completed 1980; 239214 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Continental Resources, 239213 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Cypress-Fairbanks I.S.D., 239212 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Eldridge House, 239211 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Enserch Corporation Tower, Pool Co. interiors, completed 1982; 239210 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Entex, completed 1972; 239209 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    photographs by Balthazar Korab, Seawell Photography, and Ben Smusz
  - Ewing apartments, 239208 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - George E. Failing Co., 239207 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Fannin Bank, completed 1963; 239206 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    photographs by Bisett and Dixon, Lawless and Son, Milstead Photography, and Richard Payne
  - Federated Department Stores [Foley's], 239205 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Firemen's Fund office building, 239204 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - First Methodist Church, Pasadena, 239203 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Foley's - Austin [TX] Highland Mall, 239202 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Foley's - Bryan/College Station, TX, 239201 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Foley's - Houston, 239200 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Foley's - Houston Distribution Center, completed 1978; 239199 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Foley's - Houston Greenspoint, completed 1976, 1979; 239198 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Foley's - Houston Sharpstown, completed 1961; 239197 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Foley's - Houston West Oaks and Willowbrook, completed 1982, 1981; 239196 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Foley's - San Antonio [TX] Northstar, completed 1981; 239195 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Foster Wheeler, 239194 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    photographs by Ed Stewart
  - The Galvestonian - Galveston, TX, completed 1983; 239193 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Grand Hotel, completed 1979; 239192 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Greenway Plaza, 239191 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Greenway Bank and Trust, completed 1974, 1978; 239190 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Greenway Plaza - Coastal/Summit Tower, 239189 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Greenway Plaza - Condominiums, 239188 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    photographs by Rick Gardner and sRichard Payne
  - Greenway Plaza - Houston City Club, 239187 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Greenway Plaza - Houston Design Center, completed 1984; 239186 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    photographs by Richard Payne, Steve Rosenthal
  - Greenway Plaza - Kellogg/Traveler's/Conoco Building, completed 1972, 1975, 1973; 239185 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    photographs by Rick Gardner, Alexandre Georges, Balthazar Korab, and Richard Payne
  - Greenway Plaza - Medenco Building, completed 1976; 239184 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Greenway Plaza models, 239183 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    photographs by Rick Gardner, Balthazar Korab, Photographic Laboratories, and Jim Thomas
  - Greenway Plaza - Stouffer's Hotel, completed 1976; 239182 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    photographs by Rick Gardner, Balthazar Korab, and Richard Payne
  - Greenway Plaza - Summit Arena, completed 1975; 239181 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    photographs by Rick Gardner, Harper Leiper Studios, and Balthazar Korab
  - Greenway Plaza - Summit Plaza Towers, completed 1978, 1982; 239180 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    photographs by Rick Gardner, Lawless and Son, and Richard Payne
  - Greenway Plaza - Union Carbide/Eastern Airline Towers, completed 1969, 1971; 239179 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    photographs by Bob Bailey, Balthazar Korab, Ben Smusz, and Jim Thomas
  - Gulf Envelope Company, 239178 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    photographs by Dorsey and Peters
  - Harris Moving and Storage Company, 239177 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Houston Baptist College, 239176 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Houston Baptist University - Hinton Academic Center, 239175 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Houston Natural Gas, completed 1968; 239174 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    photographs by Alexandre Georges, Harper Leiper Studios, Ed Stewart, and Jim Thomas
  - Houstonian estates Condominium, completed 1981; 239173 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    photographs by David Fisk, Rick Gardner, and Richard Payne
  - Johns-Manville Sales Corporation, 239172 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Karen Investment Company, 239171 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Kashmere Gardens Elementary School, 239170 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    photographs by Paul Dorsey and Earl R. Gilbert
  - Kinkaid School, 239169 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    photographs by Stiles and Associates
  - Kinkaid School Gym, 239168 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    photographs by F. Wilbur Seiders Associate Shoemake-Stiles
  - Kinkaid School Headmaster's residence, 239167 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - KTRK-TV, completed 1962, 1988; 239166 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lake Jackson [TX] residential units, 239165 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - [G. Burton] Liese residence, 239164 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    photographs by Foto Art Studios and F.W. Seiders
  - Linbeck Construction Company, 239163 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    photographs by Paul Dorsey
  - [802] Lovett Blvd., 239162 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Mayfair Apartment Building, completed 1955; 239161 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - McGovern Allergy Clinic, completed 1974; 239160 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - McKesson and Robbins, Inc., 239159 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Melrose Building, completed 1950; 239158 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    photographs by Jack F. Laws, Art Meyer, and F. Wilbur Seiders
  - Miami [FL] Arena, completed 1988; 239157 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    photographs by Gabriel Alonso
  - Mulberry Manor - Bellaire, TX, 239156 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Music Hall remodel, completed 1952; 239155 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National Bank of Commerce Plaza - San Antonio, TX, 239154 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Nordheim School - Nordheim, TX, 239153 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Oakbrook Park, completed 1982; 239152 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Oak Meadows, 239151 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Olympic Sports Center - Kuwait, 239150 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Orlando [FL] Arena, completed 1989; 239149 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    photographs by Marc St. Gil
  - Orlando [FL] Arena, completed 1989; 239148 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Parker Memorial Methodist Church, 239147 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Parklane Condominium, completed 1983; 239146 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pasadena I.S.D., 239145 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    photographs by Shoemake-Stiles
  - Pasadena [TX] Town Square, 239144 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Prudential Insurance Company, 239143 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    photographs by Harper Leiper Studios
  - Pyramid Arena - Memphis, TN, 239142 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - [Frank] Rembert Motel [Yupon Motor Hotel], 239141 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rembert residence, 239140 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Regency Square Office Park, 239139 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rice University - Allen Center, completed 1965; 239138 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    photographs by Alexandre Georges and Balthazar Korab
  - Rice University - Jones [Residential] College, 239137 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Rice University - Jones College Master's House, 239136 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rice University - Sewall Hall, completed 1969; 239135 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    photographs by Stan Begham, Rick Gardner, and Balthazar Korab
  - Rice University - Student Union, 239134 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rice University - Stadium, completed 1950; 239133 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    photographs by Bob Bailey and Harper Leiper Studios
  - Sam Houston Life Insurance Building, 239132 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    photographs by F.W. Seiders Associate Shoemake-Stiles
  - Sam Houston Senior High School [H.I.S.D.], 239131 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - San Antonio [TX] Savings Association, completed 1983; 239130 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    photographs by Joe C. Aker
  - Schiller Road Research Center/Office Park, completed 1984; 239129 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Second Presbyterian Church, 239128 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    photographs by W.D. Murdy
  - [Mr. and Mrs. E. Joe] Shimek residence, 239127 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    photographs by Owen Johnson (Houston Post Co.)
  - Smith Tower, 239126 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    photographs by Jennifer M. Keiger
  - South Shaver Elementary School [P.I.S.D.], completed 1949; 239125 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Center, 239124 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Southwest State Bank - Corpus Christi, TX, completed 1982; 239123 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, 239122 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - [Dr. and Mrs. Nelson C.] Steenland residence, 239121 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    photographs by F. Wilbur Seiders
  - [Robert] Straus residence, 239120 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Straus Frank Company - Dallas, TX, 239119 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    photographs by Earl R. Gilbert
  - Tealstone Condominium, completed 1983; 239118 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Tenneco Computer Science Building, completed 1973; 239117 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Texas Bank and Trust, completed 1974, 1975; 239116 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    photographs by Lawless and Son
  - Texas Commerce Bank, 239115 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Town and Country Apartments, 239114 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Tracor, Inc. - Rockville, MD, completed 1983; 239113 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - University of Houston - Hofheinz Pavilion, completed 1969; 239112 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    photographs by Richard Payne and Ed Stewart
  - University of Houston - Humanities Building, completed 1978; 239111 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - University of Houston - Women's Physical Education Building, completed 1970; 239110 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - University State Bank, completed 1981; 239109 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    photographs by Lawless Houston and Richard Payne
  - [Bernard] Weingarten residence, 239108 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Weingarten's, 239107 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    photographs by Harper Leiper Studios and George Peters
  - Wesleyan Terrace, 239106 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - West End Baptist Church, 239105 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Wetmore and Company, 239104 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Woodway Tower, completed 1980; 239103 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - unidentified projects, 239102 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Series III: Oversize, 239068
  - Allen Center rendering photographs, 239100 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Allen Center - Capital Bank photograph, 239099 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Allen Center - Capital Bank: Texas Society of Architects Honor Award for Interior Architecture (2 copies), 1981; 239098 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Allen Center - Capital Bank Heritage Club: Texas Society of Architects Honor Award for Interior Architecture, 1982; 239097 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - American General photograph, completed 1979; 239096 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - American General - Texas Society of Architects Honor Award, 1979; 239095 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Astrodome construction photograph, 1963; 239094 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    photograph by The New York Times
  - Banc Texas Allen Parkway - Texas Society of Architects Honor Award, 1984; 239093 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - [Mrs. Ann] Bart residence - Stillforest photographs, 239092 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - [Mrs. B.F.] Bart residence - Troon Road photographs, completed 1948; 239091 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Calcasieu Marine National Bank, Lake Charles, LA - Texas Society of Architects Honor Award, 1984; 239090 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Coastal Tower Lobby - Texas Society of Architects Honor Award, 1979; 239089 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Entex photographs, completed 1972; 239088 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    photographs by Harper Leiper Studios, Balthazar Korab, and John P. Miller
  - Fannin Bank photographs, 239087 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Foley's - Houston Greenspoint, completed 1976, 1979; 239086 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Greenway Plaza, 239085 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Greenway Plaza rendering - view of Kellogg and Conoco Buildings, 239084 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Greenway Plaza, Richmond Avenue Skyway - Texas Society of Architects Honor Award, 1981; 239083 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Greenway Plaza - Stouffer's Hotel, completed 1976; 239082 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Greenway Plaza, The Summit - Texas Society of Architects Honor Award, 1979; 239081 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Houston Natural Gas, completed 1968; 239080 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Liese residence, 239079 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - McKesson and Robbins, Inc. photographs, 239078 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Melrose Building photographs and renderings, completed 1950; 239077 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    photographs by Paul Dorsey, Dorsey and Peters, and F. Wilbur Seiders
  - Orlando Arena - official guide and Orlando Award of Merit, 1989; 239076 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Parker Memorial Methodist Church photographs, 239075 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    photographs by Jack Richburg
  - Rice University - Sewall Hall photographs, completed 1969; 239074 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    photographs by Balthazar Korab
  - Rice University - Stadium photographs, completed 1950; 239073 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    photographs by F.W. Seiders and Shoemake-Stiles
  - Sam Houston Senior High School photograph, 239072 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    photographs by Ralph N. Miller
  - [Robert] Straus residence photographs, 239071 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - University of Houston Women's Physical Education Building and Swimming Pool plans, July 27, 1967; 239070 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Oversize - Astrodome drawings, 239069 (Box 16, Folder -)